class AlgebraQuestion {
  final String questionText;
  final List<String> options;
  final int correctAnswerIndex;
  final int mark;

  AlgebraQuestion({
    required this.questionText,
    required this.options,
    required this.correctAnswerIndex,
    required this.mark
  });
}


final List<AlgebraQuestion> algebraQuestion  = [
   AlgebraQuestion(
    questionText: 'What is the value of x if 2x = 10?',
    options: ['4', '5', '7', '10'],
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    mark: 5,
  ),

     AlgebraQuestion(
    questionText: 'If x + 3 = 7, what is x?',
    options: ['4', '5', '10', '2'],
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    mark: 5,
  ),

      AlgebraQuestion(
    questionText: 'What is the value of 3x if x = 4?',
    options: ['4', '5', '15', '12'],
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
    mark: 5,
  ),

    AlgebraQuestion(
    questionText: 'Solve for y: y - 5 = 2',
    options: ['6', '7', '15', '12'],
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    mark: 5,
  ),

    AlgebraQuestion(
    questionText: 'If 4x = 16, what is x?',
    options: ['4', '7', '15', '5'],
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    mark: 5,
  ),

    AlgebraQuestion(
    questionText: 'What is the solution for 2x + 3 = 9?',
    options: ['4', '7', '2', '5'],
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
    mark: 5,
  ),

  AlgebraQuestion(
    questionText: 'What is x if x - 4 = 10?',
    options: ['41', '17', '14', '15'],
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
    mark: 5,
  ),

  AlgebraQuestion(
    questionText: 'What is 5 times x if x = 3?',
    options: ['41', '17', '14', '15'],
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
    mark: 5,
  ),

  AlgebraQuestion(
    questionText: 'If 6x = 18, what is x?',
    options: ['7', '3', '10', '1'],
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    mark: 5,
  ),

      AlgebraQuestion(
    questionText: 'Solve for x: x + 7 = 10',
    options: ['7', '3', '10', '1'],
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    mark: 5,
  ),

      AlgebraQuestion(
    questionText: 'What is 2x + 5 if x = 2?',
    options: ['7', '3', '9', '11'],
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
    mark: 5,
  ),

      AlgebraQuestion(
    questionText: 'What is the value of x if x/2 = 5?',
    options: ['10', '3', '9', '11'],
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    mark: 5,
  ),

     AlgebraQuestion(
    questionText: 'Solve for x: x - 6 = 4',
    options: ['7', '3', '10', '11'],
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
    mark: 5,
  ),

  
     AlgebraQuestion(
    questionText: 'If x + 8 = 14, what is x?',
    options: ['7', '3', '10', '6'],
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
    mark: 5,
  ),

    AlgebraQuestion(
    questionText: 'What is 4x if x = 3?',
    options: ['12', '21', '30', '24'],
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    mark: 5,
  ),

     AlgebraQuestion(
    questionText: 'Solve for y: y/3 = 4',
    options: ['12', '21', '30', '24'],
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    mark: 5,
  ),

     AlgebraQuestion(
    questionText: 'If 5x = 25, what is x?',
    options: ['12', '5', '3', '4'],
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    mark: 5,
  ),

    AlgebraQuestion(
    questionText: 'What is x if x - 2 = 8?',
    options: ['10', '5', '11', '16'],
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    mark: 5,
  ),

   AlgebraQuestion(
    questionText: 'What is the value of y if y - 3 = 6?',
    options: ['10', '57', '11', '9'],
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
    mark: 5,
  ),

    AlgebraQuestion(
    questionText: 'If 2x + 1 = 9, what is x?',
    options: ['2', '5', '4', '6'],
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
    mark: 5,
  ),
  
  
  

  

];